<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="107">
    <author>LimnedMoonlight</author>
    <version>1.0.0.5</version>

    <title>
        <en>Vehicle Distance-Optimizer</en>
        <fr>Vehicle Distance-Optimizer</fr>
        <de>Vehicle Distance-Optimizer</de>
    </title>

    <description>
<en><![CDATA[Optimize game performance by dynamically adjusting the visibility (clip distance) of vehicles and implements.
This mod reduces rendering load by hiding distant, unused machinery while keeping active fleet fully visible.

Github-Link: https://github.com/LimnedMoon/FS25_vehicleDistanceOptimizer/

Features:
- Automatically adjusts clip distance based on vehicle usage.
- Reduces GPU and CPU load by adjusting parked equipment.
- Distinguishes between player-controlled, AI-helper, and parked vehicles.
- Custom settings via XML file in modSettings folder.
]]></en>

<fr><![CDATA[Optimisez les performances du jeu en ajustant dynamiquement la visibilite (distance de coupure) des véhicules et des outils agricoles.
Ce mod reduit la charge de rendu en masquant les machines eloignees et inutilisees, tout en conservant une visibilite totale sur la flotte active.

Github-Link: https://github.com/LimnedMoon/FS25_vehicleDistanceOptimizer/

Caracteristiques :
- Adaptation automatique en fonction de l'etat du vehicule.
- Reduit la charge du GPU et du CPU lorsque les vehicules sont a l'arret.
- Distingue entre le vehicule du joueur, les interventions d'assistance et l'arret complet.
- Possibilite de personnaliser les parametres via un fichier XML dans le dossier modSettings.
]]></fr>

<de><![CDATA[Optimiert die Performance durch dynamische Anpassung der Sichtweite (Clip-Distance) von Fahrzeugen und Geräten.
Diese Mod reduziert die Grafiklast, indem sie weit entfernte, ungenutzte Maschinen ausblendet, während der aktive Fuhrpark voll sichtbar bleibt.

Github-Link: https://github.com/LimnedMoon/FS25_vehicleDistanceOptimizer/

Features:
- Automatische Anpassung basierend auf dem Fahrzeugstatus.
- Reduziert GPU- und CPU-Last bei geparkten Geräten.
- Unterscheidet zwischen Spieler-Fahrzeug, Helfer-Einsatz und Stillstand.
- Eigene Einstellungen über eine XML-Datei im modSettings-Ordner möglich.
]]></de>
    </description>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/VehicleDistanceOptimizer.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

</modDesc>
